const category = {
  movies: [
    {
      question: "Which famous singer appeared in the movie Mad Max: Beyond Thunderdome?",
      answer: "Tina Turner",
      options: ["Lady Gaga", "Cyndi Lauper", "Tina Turner", "Ariana Grande"]
    },
    {
      question: "Who directed the 1977 movie Star Wars?",
      answer: "George Lucas",
      options: ["George Lucas", "Steven Spielberg", "David Lynch", "Quentin Tarantino"]
    },
    {
      question: "Which action movie star was the voice of the Iron Giant?",
      answer: "Vin Diesel",
      options: ["Vin Diesel", "Tom Cruise", "Johnny Depp", "Will Smith"]
    },
    {
      question: "In what year was the movie “Grease” released?",
      answer: "1978",
      options: ["1980", "1975", "1970", "1978"]
    },
    {
      question: "In what year was the original “Jurassic Park” film released?",
      answer: "1993",
      options: ["1990", "1985", "1993", "1989"]
    },
    {
      question: "When adjusted for inflation, which is the highest grossing film of all time?",
      answer: "Gone with the wind",
      options: ["Casablanca", "Gone with the wind", "Ben-Hur", "Titanic"]
    },
    {
      question: "In movies, a clue or piece of information which is intended to be misleading, is known as what?",
      answer: "Red Herring",
      options: ["Red Herring", "Trick", "Bluff", "Ploy"]
    },
    {
      question:"What was the name of the 1999 American found footage horror film about three student filmmakers that disappeared in the woods?",
      answer: "The Blair Witch Project",
      options: ["The Woods", "The Last Exorcism", "Cloverfield", "The Blair Witch Project"]
    },
    {
      question:"Which Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle always wears red bandanas?",
      answer: "Raphael",
      options: ["Michelangelo","Leonardo","Donatello","Raphael"]
    },
    {
      question:"What did the famous Hollywood sign, located in Los Angeles, originally say?",
      answer: "Hollywoodland",
      options: ["Hollywoodland", "Fantasyland", "Dreamland", "Utopia"]
    },
    {
      question:"In the 1986 blockbuster “Top Gun” which actress played Goose’s wife?",
      answer: "Meg Ryan",
      options: ["Winona Ryder","Meg Ryan","Michelle Pfeiffer", "Julianne Moore"]
    },
    {
      question:"Who directed the movie “Reservoir Dogs”?",
      answer: "Quentin Tarantino",
      options: ["David Fincher","Spike Lee","Quentin Tarantino", "Martin Scorsese"]
    },
    {
      question: "Who played the fictional anti hero Deadpool in the 2016 movie?",
      answer: "Ryan Reynolds",
      options: ["Chris Evans","Ryan Reynolds", "Tom Hardy", "John Krasinski"]
    },
    {
      question:"Who was the female lead in the movie “Titanic”?",
      answer: "Kate Winslet",
      options: ["Kate Winslet", "Nicole Kidman", "Angelina Jolie", "Sandra Bullock"]
    },
    {
      question:"Who played Dracula in the 1931 vampire-horror film “Dracula”?",
      answer: "Bela Lugosi",
      options: ["Bela Lugosi", "Ed Wood", "Boris Karloff", "Tod Browning"]
    },
    {
      question:"The original Ghostbusters movie was released in June of what year?",
      answer: "1984",
      options: ["1984","1985","1986","1987"]
    },
    {
      question:"Tom Hanks played “Captain Miller” in what legendary World War II movie?",
      answer: "Saving Private Ryan",
      options: ["Days of Glory", "Stalingrad", "Saving Private Ryan", "Paratroop Command"]
    },
    {
      question:"Robin Williams won an Academy Award for best supporting actor in which 1997 film?",
      answer: "Good Will Hunting",
      options: ["Dead Poets Society", "Jakob the Liar", "Awakenings", "Good Will Hunting"] 
    },
    {
      question:"Who played the female lead role in the 1986 sci-fi movie “Aliens”?",
      answer: "Sigourney Weaver",
      options: ["Sigourney Weaver", "Olivia Newton-John", "Farrah Fawcett", "Barbra Streisand"]
    },
    {
      question:"What is Michael J. Fox’s middle name?",
      answer: "Andrew",
      options: ["Matthew", "Andrew", "Joshua", "Anthony"]
    },
    {
      question:"In what year was Alfred Hitchcock’s psychological thriller “Psycho” released?",
      answer: "1960",
      options: ["1965", "1960", "1970", "1968"]
    },
    {
      question:"What is the name of the 1978 movie, about an American college student who is sent to a Turkish prison for attempting to smuggle hashish out of Turkey?",
      answer: "Midnight Express",
      options: ["Brokedown Palace", "Midnight Express", "American Made", "Wings of Danger"]
    },
    {
      question:"In which 1993 thriller does the protagonist violently lose his cool when a fast food restaurant will not let him order from the breakfast menu?",
      answer:"Falling Down",
      options: ["Falling Down", "Pulp Fiction", "Die Hard", "Jackie Brown"]
    },
    {
      question:"Which actress played identical twins in the 1998 movie remake of The Parent Trap?",
      answer:"Lindsay Lohan",
      options: ["Demi Lovato", "Anne Hathaway", "Elizabeth Olsen", "Lindsay Lohan"]
    },
    {
      question:"In the movie “The Wizard of Oz”, what did the Scarecrow want from the wizard?",
      answer:"A brain",
      options: ["A heart", "A brain", "Courage", "Freedom"]
    },
    {
      question:"The first movie of the Fast and Furious franchise was released in what year?",
      answer: "2001",
      options: ["1996", "1998", "2001", "2003"]
    },
    {
      question:"Tyler Durden is a ficitional character appearing as the central protagonist and antagonist in what 1999 American film?",
      answer: "Fight Club",
      options: ["The Game", "Memento", "Fight Club", "Zodiac"]
    },
    {
      question:"Who played the female lead in the 1942 film Casablanca?",
      answer: "Ingrid Bergman",
      options: ["Grace Kelly", "Elizabeth Taylor", "Ingrid Bergman", "Debbie Reynolds"]
    },
    {
      question:"Actress Gal Gadot starred in what American superhero film released in the summer of 2017?",
      answer: "Wonder Woman",
      options: ["Wonder Woman", "Black Widow", "Nebula", "Scarlet Witch"]
    },
    {
      question:"Who played the female lead in the 1990 romantic comedy Pretty Woman?",
      answer: "Julia Roberts",
      options: ["Jodie Foster", "Jeniffer Aniston","Sandra Bullock", "Julia Roberts"]
    }
  ],
  animals: [
    {
      question: "What is the largest animal currently on Earth?",
      answer: "Blue Whale",
      options: ["Whale Shark", "Blue Whale", "African Bush Elephant", "Brown Bear"]
    },
    {
      question: "Lemurs, a type of primate, are native to what island nation?",
      answer: "Madagascar",
      options: ["New Guinea", "Bali", "Madagascar", "Tahiti"]
    },
    {
      question: "Su Lin was the name given to what type of animal captured in China and brought to the United States for the first time in 1936?",
      answer: "Giant Panda",
      options: ["Koala", "Giant Panda", "Red Panda", "Amur Leopard"]
    },
    {
      question: "Which animal is the tallest in the world?",
      answer: "Giraffe",
      options: ["Giraffe", "Elephant", "Ostrich", "Brown Bear"]
    },
    {
      question: "What type of animal is known as the ship of the desert?",
      answer: "Camel",
      options: ["Arabian Oryx", "Camel", "Desert Iguana", "Cougar"]
    },
    {
      question: "On what continent would you not find bees?",
      answer: "Antarctica",
      options: ["Australia", "Asia", "Antarctica", "Africa"]
    },
    {
      question: "Which animal has the largest brain?",
      answer: "Sperm Whale",
      options: ["Sperm Whale", "Octopus", "Grey Kangaroo", "Dolphin"]
    },
    {
      question: "Which animal has the longest gestation period?",
      answer: "Elephant",
      options: ["Elephant", "Whale", "Rhinoceros", "Giraffe"]
    },
    {
      question: "An animal that lives part of its life on land and part in water is known as what?",
      answer: "Amphibian",
      options: ["Mammal", "Amphibian", "Reptiles", "Insects"]
    },
    {
      question: "A koala’s diet consists mainly of what?",
      answer: "Eucalyptus leaves",
      options: ["Eucalyptus leaves", "Fruits", "Urine", "Bamboo"]
    },
    {
      question: "What animal has the fastest metabolism?",
      answer: "Hummingbird",
      options: ["Pigeon", "Elephant", "Cow", "Hummingbird"]
    },
    {
      question: "In the United States which breed of dog is commonly known as a firehouse dog?",
      answer: "Dalmatian",
      options: ["German Shepherd", "Dalmatian", "Great Dane", "Beagle"]
    },
    {
      question: "How many chambers are there in a dog’s heart?",
      answer: "Four",
      options: ["Two", "Four", "Nine", "Twelve"]
    },
    {
      question: "An octopus can fit through any hole larger than its what?",
      answer: "Beak",
      options: ["Leg", "Beak", "Head", "Stomach"]
    },
    {
      question: "Now extinct, what shark is thought to have been the largest ever on Earth?",
      answer: "Megalodon",
      options: ["Megalodon", "Mega Whale", "Purple Shark", "African Black Elephant"]
    },
    {
      question: "Snoopy from the comic peanuts is what breed of dog?",
      answer: "Beagle",
      options: ["Dachshund", "Beagle", "Siberian Husky", "Labrador Retriever"]
    },
    {
      question: "What was the name of Robert E. Lee’s most famous horse?",
      answer: "Traveller",
      options: ["Traveller", "Silver", "Spirit", "Thunder"]
    },
    {
      question: "What is the fastest land snake in the world?",
      answer: "Black Mamba",
      options: ["Sidewinder Snake", "Black Mamba", "Southern Black Racer", "Cottonmouth Viper"]
    },
    {
      question: "Which animal has the most legs?",
      answer: "Millipede",
      options: ["Centipede", "Millipede", "Thousenpede", "Muitopede"]
    },
    {
      question: "What is the fastest fish in the Ocean?",
      answer: "Sailfish",
      options: ["Black Marlin", "Swordfish", "Wahoo", "Sailfish"]
    },
    {
      question: "The Alaskan Malamute is a type of what?",
      answer: "Dog",
      options: ["Dog", "Cat", "Goat", "Fish"]
    },
    {
      question: "Polar bears feed mainly on what animal?",
      answer: "Seal",
      options: ["Moose", "Deer", "Fish", "Seal"]
    },
    {
      question: "What is the sleepiest animal in the world, sleeping around 22 hours each day?",
      answer: "Koala",
      options: ["Cat", "Sloth", "Opossum", "Koala"]
    },
    {
      question: "Which bird is often associated with delivering babies?",
      answer: "Stork",
      options: ["Gull", "Stork", "Heron", "Pelican"]
    },
    {
      question: "How many hearts does an octopus have?",
      answer: "Three",
      options: ["Three", "Four", "Five", "Six"]
    },
    {
      question: "In the United States, where can alligators and crocodiles be found together in the wild?",
      answer: "Florida",
      options: ["Texas", "Washington", "Hawaii", "Florida"]
    },
    {
      question: "What is the national animal of Scotland?",
      answer: "Unicorn",
      options: ["Dragon", "Unicorn", "Dragonfly", "Dinosaur"]
    },
    {
      question: "What animal has the largest ears?",
      answer: "Elephant",
      options: ["Hare", "Elephant", "Bat", "Basset"]
    },
    {
      question: "The Chihuahua is a breed of dog believed to originate from what country?",
      answer: "Mexico",
      options: ["Mexico", "Colombia", "Peru", "Costa Rica"]
    },
    {
      question: "Cynophobia is the fear of what kind of animal?",
      answer: "Dogs",
      options: ["Cats", "Dogs", "Birds", "Rabbits"]
    }
  ],
  food: [
    {
      question: "The United States state of Georgia is famous for what fruit?",
      answer:"Peach",
      options: ["Grape", "Peach", "Apple", "Orange"],
    },
    {
      question:"What is the main ingredient in guacamole?",
      answer:"Avocado",
      options: ["Avocado", "Jalapeño", "Red Onion", "Lemon"],
    },
    {
      question:"How many items are in a bakers dozen?",
      answer:"13",
      options: ["11", "12", "13", "14"],
    },
    {
      question:"What popular beverage once contained cocaine?",
      answer:"Coca-Cola",
      options: ["Coca-Cola", "Brazilian Guarana", "Fanta", "Pepsi"],
    },
    {
      question:"What is the name of the first pizzeria to open in the United States?",
      answer:"Lombardi's Pizza",
      options: ["Giuseppi's Pizza", "Antonio's Pizza", "Luigi's Pizza", "Lombardi's Pizza"],
    },
    {
      question:"Bubble tea originated in which country?",
      answer:"Taiwan",
      options: ["China", "Taiwan", "Haiti", "Indonesia"],
    },
    {
      question:"The desire to eat strange things that are non-nutritive is known as what?",
      answer:"Pica",
      options: ["Tica", "Cica", "Pica", "Mica"],
    },
    {
      question:"In what year was the blue M&M first introduced?",
      answer:"1995",
      options: ["1993", "1994", "1995", "1996"],
    },
    {
      question:"In the US, a pint of milk is equal to how many cups of milk?",
      answer:"Two",
      options: ["One", "Two", "Three", "Four"],
    },
    {
      question:"Where was the fortune cookie invented?",
      answer:"California",
      options: ["California", "Colorado", "New Jersey", "Alaska"],
    },
    {
      question:"Paella, a famous rice dish, originated in what country?",
      answer:"Spain",
      options: ["Italy", "Portugal", "Spain", "France"],
    },
    {
      question:"Which liquor is made from the blue agave plant?",
      answer:"Tequila",
      options: ["Tequila", "Gin", "Cachaça", "Rum"],
    },
    {
      question:"What ingredient in bread causes it to rise?",
      answer:"Yeast",
      options: ["Sugar", "Salt", "Water", "Yeast"],
    },
    {
      question:"Gumbo is a stew that originated in which state?",
      answer:"Louisiana",
      options: ["Alabama", "Mississipi", "Louisiana", "Georgia"],
    },
    {
      question:"What is the highest number of Michelin stars a restaurant can receive?",
      answer:"Three",
      options: ["Three", "Five", "Seven", "Ten"],
    },
    {
      question:"Kopi luwak is a very expensive type of what?",
      answer:"Coffee",
      options: ["Tea", "Coffee", "Salt", "Pepper"],
    },
    {
      question:"A tandoor is a type of what?",
      answer:"Oven",
      options: ["Bread", "Oven", "Spice", "Salsa"],
    },
    {
      question:"A teetotaler is a person that never drinks what?",
      answer:"Alcohol",
      options: ["Water", "Alcohol", "Juice", "Tea"],
    },
    {
      question:"What is a traditional fermented Korean side dish made seasoned vegetables and salt?",
      answer:"Kimchi",
      options: ["Rice Cake", "Kimchi", "Oi Muchim", "Gaji Namul"],
    },
    {
      question:"Chimichurri is a green sauce that originated in what country?",
      answer:"Argentina",
      options: ["India", "Mexico", "Argentina", "Spain"],
    },
    {
      question:"Pho is a popular noodle soup from what country?",
      answer:"Vietnam",
      options: ["Iraq", "Vietnam", "Cambodia", "Thailand"],
    },
    {
      question:"n French cuisine, what is the name for the following: béchamel sauce, espagnole sauce, hollandaise sauce, tomato sauce, and velouté sauce?",
      answer:"Mother Sauces",
      options: ["Combo Sauces", "Mother Sauces", "The Sauces", "Honey Sauces"],
    },
    {
      question:"In what type of restaurant would you typically find the condiment wasabi?",
      answer:"Japanese",
      options: ["Chinese", "Japanese", "Korean", "American"],
    },
    {
      question:"The cooking technique that involves submerging food in a liquid at a relatively low temperature is called what?",
      answer:"Poaching",
      options: ["Deep Fry", "Poaching", "Bain-Marie", "Thaw"],
    },
    {
      question:"What is the name for a confection that consists primarily of sugar or honey and almond meal?",
      answer:"Marzipan",
      options: ["Custard", "Marzipan", "Pastry cream", "Caramel"],
    },
    {
      question:"Sauerkraut is made from what finely cut vegetable?",
      answer:"Cabbage",
      options: ["Onion", "Cabbage", "Brussels Sprout", "Radish"],
    },
    {
      question:"What was the original flavor of the filling in Twinkies?",
      answer:"Banana cream",
      options: ["Chocolate cream", "Banana cream", "Strawberry cream", "Lemon cream"],
    },
    {
      question:"Pupusas, handmade thick stuffed corn tortillas, are a traditional dish from what country?",
      answer:"El Salvador",
      options: ["Mexico", "Spain", "El Salvador", "Uruguay"],
    },
    {
      question:"The use of chopsticks originated in what country?",
      answer:"China",
      options: ["Japan", "Korea", "China", "Taiwan"],
    },
    {
      question:"In what year did McDonald’s start serving breakfast with the introduction of the Egg McMuffin?",
      answer:"1972",
      options: ["1972", "1982", "1992", "2002"],
    }
  ],
  sports: [
    {
      question:"In what year was the first modern Olympic Games held?",
      answer:"1896",
      options: ["1896", "1900", "1923", "1945"]
    },
    {
      question:"Which athlete has won the most Olympic medals?",
      answer:"Michael Phelps",
      options: ["Larisa Latynina", "Marit Bjorgen", "Michael Phelps", "Nikolai Andrianov"]
    },
    {
      question:"In which sport does the bowler deliver the ball to the batsman?",
      answer:"Cricket",
      options: ["Baseball", "Cricket", "Punchball", "Kickball"]
    },
    {
      question:"In what country did table tennis originate?",
      answer:"England",
      options: ["England", "Korea", "Irland", "Australia"]
    },
    {
      question:"Where did the sport of curling originate?",
      answer:"Scotland",
      options: ["England", "Scotland", "Irland", "Germany"]
    },
    {
      question:"The Walker Law passed in 1920 in New York was a law regulating which sport?",
      answer:"Boxing",
      options: ["Football", "Boxing", "Tennis", "Soccer"]
    },
    {
      question:"The Grand Slam tournaments are the four most import annual events in which two sports?",
      answer:"Tennis & Golf",
      options: ["Golf & Cricket", "Tennis & Golf", "Tennis & Cricket", "Cricket & Chess"]
    },
    {
      question:"Shaquille Rashaun O’Neal retired in 2011 from what sport?",
      answer:"Basketball",
      options: ["Baseball", "Basketball", "Football", "Tennis"]
    },
    {
      question:"The Kangaroo Hoppet is a long distance cross-country skiing race that is held in which county?",
      answer:"Australia",
      options: ["New Zeland", "Taiwan", "Australia", "Indonesia"]
    },
    {
      question:"Which five-times Grand Slam tennis champion tested positive for a banned substance at the 2016 Australian Open?",
      answer:"Maria Sharapova",
      options: ["Maria Sharapova", "Caroline Wozniacki", "Alexander Gilkes", "Rafael Nadal"]
    },
    {
      question:"What is the highest score possible in 10 pin bowling?",
      answer:"300",
      options: ["300", "400", "500", "600"]
    },
    {
      question:"What sport does Cristiano Ronaldo play?",
      answer:"Soccer",
      options: ["Tennis", "Soccer", "Football", "Baseball"]
    },
    {
      question:"The Stanley Cup is a championship trophy awarded annually to the playoff winner in what sport?",
      answer:"Hockey",
      options: ["Ski", "Hockey", "Ice Skating", "Bobsleigh"]
    },
    {
      question:"What country was host to the 1930 inaugural FIFA Football World Cup?",
      answer:"Uruguay",
      options: ["Brazil", "Uruguay", "Italy", "China"]
    },
    {
      question:"Which tennis player has won the most men’s Grand Slam titles?",
      answer:"Roger Federer",
      options: ["Rafael Nadal", "Roger Federer", "Pete Sampras", "Novak Djokovic"]
    },
    {
      question:"What is professional wrestler John Cena’s famous catchphrase?",
      answer:"You can’t see me!",
      options: ["Come get me!", "F* you!", "You can’t see me!", "Peekaboo!"]
    },
    {
      question:"Anthony Jerome “Spud” Webb retired from what professional sport in 1997?",
      answer:"Basketball",
      options: ["Baseball", "Soccer", "Basketball", "Golf"]
    },
    {
      question:"The Heisman Memorial Trophy is awarded annually to the most outstanding player in which college sport?",
      answer:"Football",
      options: ["Hockey", "Football", "Cricket", "Chess"]
    },
    {
      question:"“Game, set, match” is an expression used to indicate a competitor has won the game in which sport?",
      answer:"Tennis",
      options: ["Golf", "Cricket", "Chess", "Tennis"]
    },
    {
      question:"In boxing, what is the term for an illegal punch to the back of the head or base of the skull?",
      answer:"Rabbit Punch",
      options: ["Squirrel Punch", "The No-No Punch", "Rabbit Punch", "Hare Punch"]
    },
    {
      question:"In 2012, Magic Johnson became part owner of which Major League Baseball team?",
      answer:"Los Angeles Dodgers",
      options: ["New York Mets", "Los Angeles Dodgers", "Toronto Blue Jays", "Los Angeles Angels"]
    },
    {
      question:"MMA is the acronym for what full-contact combat sport?",
      answer:"Mixed Martial Arts",
      options: ["Mixed Martial Arts", "Motal Martial Arts", "Maximum Martial Arts", "Most Martial Arts"]
    },
    {
      question:"Which water sport is the official state individual sport of Hawaii?",
      answer:"Surfing",
      options: ["Kayak Surfing", "Snorkeling", "Surfing", "Underwater Scooter"]
    },
    {
      question:"What is the name of both the championship game of the Canadian Football League and the trophy awarded to the victorious team?",
      answer:"The Grey Cup",
      options: ["The Golden Cup", "The Grey Cup", "The Pink Cup", "The Red Cup"]
    },
    {
      question:"A. J. Foyt was the first race car driver to win what race four times?",
      answer:"The Indianapolis 500",
      options: ["Formula 1", "The Indianapolis 500", "IndyCar", "Formula GM Lotus"]
    },
    {
      question:"St. Augustine Florida is the home to the hall of fame for what sport?",
      answer:"Golf",
      options: ["Tennis", "Soccer", "Golf", "Baseball"]
    },
    {
      question:"Indianapolis 500 winners traditionally celebrate by drinking what?",
      answer:"Milk",
      options: ["Champagne", "Milk", "Coca-Cola", "Red Wine"]
    },
    {
      question:"Handsome Dan is a bulldog who serves as the mascot of which university’s sports teams?",
      answer:"Yale University",
      options: ["Harvard University", "MIT", "Yale University", "Georgia Tech"]
    },
    {
      question:"How many soccer players should be on the field at the same time?",
      answer:"22",
      options: ["18", "20", "22", "24"]
    },
    {
      question:"Where is the baseball hall of fame located?",
      answer:"New York",
      options: ["California", "Texas", "New York", "Florida"]
    }
  ]
}

function getRandomMovieQuestion() {
  return category.movies[Math.floor(Math.random() * category.movies.length)]
}

function getRandomAnimalQuestion() {
  return category.animals[Math.floor(Math.random() * category.animals.length)]
}

function getRandomFoodQuestion() {
  return category.food[Math.floor(Math.random() * category.food.length)]
}

function getRandomSportQuestion() {
  return category.sports[Math.floor(Math.random() * category.sports.length)]
}

export {
  getRandomAnimalQuestion, getRandomFoodQuestion, getRandomMovieQuestion, getRandomSportQuestion
}